目 前 资 金
最 新 余 额
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
■
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
打工
姐妹花
第六集
第叁季
打工
姐妹花
第六集
第叁季
\h翻校  狂掉头发赛太公
\h翻校  失眠暴怒YY猫
后期  灰灰是菇凉\h
时间轴 总监  失眠暴怒YY猫 \h
我结算了小蛋糕店的收银机
Oh, I closed out the cupcake register.
这是挣来的房租钱
Here's our rent money.
钱拿去  信封袋还我
Gimme back the envelope though,
那袋子也是我的珠宝首饰盒
'cause it's also my jewelry box.
我也结算了收银机
I closed out the register.
我这也有一份交房租的钱
I have our rent money.
麦克斯  你知道这代表什么吗
Max, do you know what this means?
如果我脑子没有被驴踢了
Unless I was hit in the head by a piece of farm equipment,
就表示咱们有盈余啦
it means we have extra money.
我好想来一段盈余庆祝舞
I wanna do the extra money dance,
但我们没有这一套舞
but we don't have one
因为我们的钱从没有过盈余
because we've never had extra money!
我唯一会的挣钱[盈余]舞
The only extra money dance I know
需要用到乒乓球
involves ping-pong balls
又名"十八招"  常由东南亚女性表演
由下阴"吞入""喷吐"乒乓球的成人表演
而我也久没跳  技艺生疏了
and I'm really out of practice.
厄尔  我给你带来了你的最爱
Earl, I brought you your favorite.
黑人华人混血肚皮舞女吗
A half-black, half-Chinese belly dancer?
椰子味小蛋糕啦
A coconut cupcake.
你看卡洛琳
Look at Caroline over there.
使出浑身解数跟人调情
She's flirting harder with him
比我对抗心脏病还卖力
than I flirt with heart disease.
不许  不许说
Stop, stop!
人家才看到第一季第二集
I'm only on episode two of season one.
敢说人家打死你
I will kill you!
那...  下回分晓吧
Then... to be continued.
那就是还有下回咩
Oh! It's gonna be continued.
好呀  那我们下回分晓时
Well, then, we will continue this
再来下回分晓吧
when we continue this.
如果你尽全力就这程度
If that's your game,
那估计你这辈子都得跟姐住了  妹子
you're gonna be living with me forever, fran.
他已经连续叁晚来我这区
He's been in my section three nights in a row
点火鸡肉叁明治了
for the turkey club.
我叫他"火鸡叁明治帅哥"
I'm calling him "the turkey club cutie".
听得我想"叫救命"
I'm calling poison control.
我看他应该差不多要约我了
I think he's getting ready to ask me out.
他问我是不是住在附近
He wanted to know if I live around here
还问我几点下班
and what time I get off.
一个愿意等到你下班[高潮]的男人
If a man's gonna wait for you to get off,
绝对要留住啊
he's a keeper.
那就...
So...
下次见啦
See you next time.
那我们就下次见啦
I will see you next time as well.
再见
Bye.
-那是什么  -不知道  我哪会知道
- What's that? - I don't know. How would I know?
因为是你头上掉下来的啊
Because it came out of your head.
麦克斯  我才没有去接发
I don't have hair extensions, Max.
好吧  那我拿去扔了
Okay, I'll throw it out.
别  下次能当故事说
No! I'll keep it for this story!
什么故事
What story?
某天晚上我们
The story about how we found
无缘无故发现一段金色接发的故事
a blonde hair extension out of nowhere that night.
超好笑啊
It's hilarious!
是比你大多数故事都好笑了
Well, it's already funnier than most of your stories.
你看  又一段"爆笑故事"
Oh, look, there's another hilarious story!
好啦  麦克斯  我得坦白件事
Okay, Max, I have a confession to make.
我有做过接发
I have hair extensions.
我也有件事想坦白
I also have a confession to make.
我在罗德岛杀过人
I murdered a man in Rhode island.
我就接了几段  让头发有点层次
I just have a few. It gives me volume.
可惜它不能让你有点深度
Too bad it doesn't give you depth.
我现在得想办法把它们重新接上
Now I have to go and try and reattach these.
这接发不应该这么容易掉啊
These weaves are supposed to last.
我真不敢"接"信会这样
This is unbe-weave-able!
我在生菜里发现了这个
I found this in the lettuce.
里面有发现阴道避孕环吗
Any sign of a nuva ring in there?
因为我的不见了
'Cause I can't find mine.
是卡洛琳在掉头发吧
Caroline's losing her hair, isn't she?
她是不是生病了
Is she sick?
她是不是得了癌    得了大"C"[癌]
Does she have cancer, the big "C"?
才不是  小东西
No, little you.
她没有"大C"
She doesn't have the big "C".
她连"AA"罩杯都没有
She barely has the double "A"s.
阿憨发现了你的头发
Han found more of your hair.
他知道我接发的事了吗
He knows about the extensions?
没  他以为你得了癌
No, he thinks you have cancer.
那就好  没人知道就好
Oh, good! So no one knows.
安安  姑娘们  今夜因我而性感啦
Hola, ladies! Your night just got sexier.
路易斯  你早就下班了
Luis, you punched out hours ago.
你这么晚还来餐厅干嘛
What are you doing here so late?
回基[家]的路上吗
On your way homo?
牙尖嘴利呀  小贱人
Good one, hooker!
我在夜店跑摊
No, I'm between clubs.
马戏夜店现在是直男吧了
Circus just became a straight club,
卫星夜店还得再等半小时  才会变成基吧
And satellite doesn't become a gay club for a half hour.
所以就来跟我兄弟奥列格喝杯鸡尾酒啦
So...I'm here to have a cocktail with my bro Oleg.
路易斯  跟你说过他是直男了
Luis, we told you. Oleg is straight.
拜托  我在阿拉巴马州也是直男
Oh, please! So am I in Alabama.
阿拉巴马州反对同性恋
学校老师必须教导学生同性恋是违法的
他已经走了
Well, he left already.
我都跟他说我会来坐坐了
But I told him I was gonna stop by.
男人都这样  惧怕亲密感情
Typical man. Fear of intimacy.
卡洛琳儿  趁我过来
Oh, Carolina, while I'm here...
顺便把我上班发现的东西还你
This is yours. I found it during my shift.
我没拿走的小费吗
Ooh, tips from my tables?
是你没收好的头发
More like hair from your head.
我就知道你那头秀发不可能是真的
I knew this was all too good to be true.
你做了接发
You have extensions.
不是  我是得了癌
No, I have cancer.
屁咧  你做了接发  少唬我
No, you have extensions. Good try.
回见
Later!
看出我有何改变吗
Hey. Notice anything different?
我用小店盈余去弄了新接发
I took some of the extra money and got new hair extensions.
我还给你准备了份礼物  放你房里了
And I also got you a surprise. I put it in your room.
去看看
Go look!
我感兴趣的只有大肚猪
I'm not interested unless it's a potbelly pig
打扮成早期移民的大肚猪
or a potbelly pig in a pilgrim costume,
或打扮成大肚猪的早期移民
or a pilgrim in a potbelly pig costume,
或大麻[肚]
or just pot.
提示  我放在你床上哦
Hint, hint. I put it on your bed.
觉得如何  爱不爱啊
What do you think? Do you love?
为啥这坨屎会在我床上
Okay... why is all this crap on my bed?
这他妈是什么玩意啊
And what the hell is it?
这是床裙啊
That's a bed skirt.
我的床才不要穿裙子  它是大老爷们
My bed doesn't wear skirts. It's a dude!
看它在我睡觉时从背后顶我  就知道是爷们
I know, because it pokes me in the back while I'm asleep.
我帮你买了新寝具
I got you new bedding,
帮自己买了套新法兰绒睡衣
and me some cute new flannel jammies.
上面还有埃菲尔铁塔的图案
They have eiffel towers on them.
大家都讨厌法国人  所以这衣服超便宜的
They were marked down because everybody hates French people.
这上面连"污渍"都没有
These don't even have stains!
这样我怎么知道哪边是上面
How am I gonna know which is the top now?
麦克斯  这有啥不好
Max, what's the problem?
你的旧床单都用多久了
You've had those old sheets forever.
你连替换的都没有
You don't even have a spare set.
替换的床单
A spare set of sheets?
你当我谁啊  英国女皇吗
Who am I, the queen of England?
你真没劲  气得我都想扯头发了
You're so frustrating, I'd pull my hair out...
但我怕不小心扯到接发
But I'm not sure which of it is mine.
你看  这下你高兴了吗
Look! Look! Are you happy?
栗宝都不开心了  他知道我们吵架
Chestnut's upset. He knows we're fighting.
很好
Good!
是该让他知道哪天他出门买包薯片
He should know that if he goes out for a bag of chips,
很可能一回来
he could come home to find
就发现他的马鞍被换成丁字裤了
you replaced his saddle with a thong.
我可是送你礼物呢
I got you a present.
你会气  诞老人吗
Would you be this angry at Santa Claus?
他是谁啊
Who's that?
求你了  麦克斯
Max, please.
做点改变  睡在好寝具上面嘛
Just for a change, try sleeping on something nice.
行
Fine!
但我要真想睡在好寝具上面
But if I wanted to sleep on something nice,
我就跟那个搬回家照顾
I would have hooked up with that guy
生病老母亲的男人走就好了
who moved home to take care of his sick mother.
小心提防啊  栗宝
Watch your back, Chestnut.
防火防盗防小人
Watch your back.
你个贱人  我的旧寝具呢
Where are my old sheets, bitch?
为什么
Why?
为什么要大半夜骂我贱人
Why are you calling me a "bitch" at night?
人家穿着新睡衣睡觉呢
I was sleeping in my new jammies.
没我的旧寝具我睡不着
Well, I can't sleep without those sheets.
你所有抽屉我都看过了  你藏哪去了
So where are they? I checked all your drawers.
对了
And by the way,
谁会把电动棒收星巴克杯子里啊
Who hides their vibrator in a Starbucks cup?
明知故问  我继续睡觉了
You already know the answer, so I'm going back to sleep.
为什么呀
Why!
为什么穿着新睡衣的我会在地上
Why am I on the floor in my new jammies?
到底放哪去了
Where are they?
不在我这  我送给穷人了
I don't have them. I gave them to the poor.
你从穷人那里偷过去的
You took them from the poor!
现在穷人想讨回来
And the poor wants them back.
已经迟了
Well, it's too late.
我放到救世军的慈善捐助箱了
I put them in the Salvation Army donation bin.
那起来  你得去军中一趟了  贱妇
Well, get up. You're going to the army, bitch.
为什么呀
Whyyyy?
为什么我们大半夜得跑来这里
Why are we here in the middle of the night?
我们要干嘛
What are we doing?
就在这了  跟我过来
Here it is. Come on, follow me.
麦克斯  你要在这杀我吗
Max, is this where you kill me?
我一直都知道会有这么一天
'Cause I always knew it was gonna happen,
但我不知何时会发生
I just didn't know when.
但这里很有那感觉啊
This feels right though.
我是应该宰了你
I should kill you.
那套寝具对我有很特别的意义好吗
Those sheets were really special to me, okay?
你在上面失去贞操的吗
Oh, did you lose your virginities on them?
我不在床上做爱  那是我吃饭的地方
I don't have sex in beds. That's where I eat.
卡洛琳  我有件事要坦白
Caroline, I have a confession.
-什么事  -你有接发
- What is it? - You have hair extensions.
好啦  我说  但你不许看我
Okay, I'll tell you, but look away.
重点是那个枕套  我小时候就开始用了
It's the pillowcase. I've had it since I was a kid.
它又软又有触感
It's like soft and nubby
还有边边  我可以摸
and it had this edge that I'd like...rub,
在倒霉的日子  也就是每一天
and it relaxed me when things were crappy,
都能让我放松
which was all the time.
我需要那个枕套才能睡着
I guess I still need that pillowcase to sleep or whatever.
麦克斯  你好可怜哦
Max, that's so sad.
当然可怜啊
Of course it's sad!
我有过欢乐童话故事吗
When has it ever been a happy tale?
好啦  我得爬进去
All right, I need to crawl in here.
麦克斯  你要爬进这脏箱子啊
Max, you're just gonna crawl into that dirty box?
我们都不知道这箱子有多脏
We don't know where that bin's been.
对了
By the way,
"脏箱子"[脏货]也是我当年在学校的绰号
"dirty box" was my nickname in continuation school.
帮忙一下
I need help.
你是要我踩你背上  还是踩你的头
Would you rather I step on your back or your head?
想都别想  这么贵的头会给你踩吗
My head? Hardly. Not at these prices.
来吧  十根手指伸出来
Come on, gimme ten fingers.
给过了
I already did.
来的路上伸过十次中指
Behind your back while we were walking here.
是让你这样  我就能踩着上去
No, like this, so I can step into it.
就跟个手指篮子一样
You know, like a finger basket.
手指篮[装蛋蛋]
Finger basket?
那是你的另一个绰号吗
Is that another nickname of yours?
不是  但某年夏天本来可以的
No, but for one summer, it could've been.
那算了  来帮忙搬东西让我踩吧
Forget this, just let me pull this stuff over.
麦克斯  我觉得我们一直在突破下限
Max, I feel like we're not even acknowledging
下限都成路人了
our low points anymore.
麦克斯  千万小心
Okay, Max, now be very careful.
等我数到...
And on the count of...
你完全能当体操员啊
Wow! You could've been a great gymnast,
如果你有钱  有教练  做了缩胸手术的话
if you'd had money, coaches, and a breast reduction.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
麦克斯
Max?
发点声音出来啊
Gonna need some voice contact.
吾路不孤
I'm not in here alone.
你说吾路不孤是个什么意思
What do you mean you're not alone?
意思是  里面不只我一个人
I mean, I'm not in here alone.
别慌  我马上救你出来
Stay calm! I will get you out of there.
不  我做不到
No, I won't.
我在找打开门的把手
I'm looking for a lever on the inside.
滚出我家
Get outta my house!
我只是想看看你是不是压在我的枕套上
I just wanna check and see if you're on my pillowcase.
-别啊  麦克斯  -我要我亲爱的寝具
- Max, no! - I need my sweet sheets!
放弃吧
Let it go.
如果被他压在身下了  那也不亲不爱了
If your sheets are under there, they're no long sweet.
滚出我家
Get outta my house!
关上门
Close the door!
行行行
Okay! Okay!
真是的  咱俩也算睡过了  真无情
God, sheez. You'd think we'd slept together.
这下我得怎么办
What am I gonna do?
没那套寝具我就睡不着
I can't sleep without those sheets.
我恨死你了
I'm so angry at you!
要不是发现这件好奶罩  我会更气
I'd be even angrier if I hadn't found this great bra.
你想睡觉为啥还要来苏菲家
Why are you going to Sophie's if you're trying to sleep?
她是我们认识最大嗓门的人了
She's the loudest person we know.
电影院里爱喧哗的黑人都嫌她吵
Even black people at the movies tell Sophie to be quiet.
我来她家是想要个安眠药
I am going to Sophie's to get a sleeping pill.
也就是她口中的"晚安糖"
Or as she likes to call them, "night candy".
你不需要吃安眠药
You don't need a pill.
我有一招很棒的入眠方法
Listen, I have a great sleep technique
是我的睡眠教练教我的
that my sleep coach taught me.
我也跟一堆教练"睡"过
I have slept with my fair share of coaches,
他们的唯一用处就是让我不能睡
and if anything, they kept me awake.
麦克斯  凌晨叁点
Max, it's 3:00 A.M.
正常人应该都睡了
Any normal person is sleeping right now.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
我一边听猫王  一边拼拼图呢
Just doing a puzzle and listening to Elvis.
趁你们还没累累  先来杯酒酒吧
You two want a mai tai before you get too ty-ty?
不用了  但说到累累
No, thanks, but speaking of ty-ty,
我想问你要一颗安眠药
I was hoping I could snag one of your sleeping pills.
没问题  我能给你
Oh, sure, I can hook you up.
我从来不用
I never use them.
我晚上都只需要睡叁小时
I only need three hours of sleep at night
白天再睡个六小时  进来吧
and six during the day. Come on.
苏菲
Sophie...
发现哪里是新的吗
Notice anything new?
有啊
Oh! Yeah!
你头上接了更多头发吗
You planted more hair on your head.
我听说了
I heard.
麦克斯  你居然告诉她
Max! You told her?
没  这事都上新闻联播了
No, it was on CNN.
先报导了叙利亚的新闻
They led with Syria,
然后连续报道了五分钟你头发的事
and then did a solid five on your hair.
来啦  药跟香料
Here we go-- pills and spices!
你有满香料架的药吗
You have a spice rack full of pills?
改天下厨做顿晚餐请我吃吧
You gotta cook me dinner sometime.
我看看
Let's see.
鱼油  盘尼西林  阿莫西林
Fish oil, penicillin, amoxicillin...
彩虹糖
Skittles.
这是我的德国神药
Oh, and this is my German pill
哪天核弹大爆发  还是我被放逐外星时吃
in case they release the bombs or I'm ever abandoned in space.
给  麦克斯  睡个好觉
Here you go, Max. Nighty-night.
这样吧
Oh, you know what?
管这么多干嘛  老娘也来一粒
What the hell! I'm gonna have one too.
这是睡衣派对
It's a slumber party!
你又有另一架子[胸部]的药了
Oh, now you got another rack full of pills.
算了吧
Oh, you know what?
别等我了  麦克斯  估计得找一会
Don't wait for me, Max. This might be a while.
麦克斯  你真的得靠药物吗
Max, do you really need to take that?
吃完安眠药  很多人会做怪事
People do weird things on sleeping pills.
我一个朋友
My friend Candice Travelstead
梦游用奶油涂满皮夹  还打算吃下去
buttered a wallet and tried to eat it.
别担心  我没皮夹
Don't worry, I don't have a wallet.
等等  等等
Wait a minute! Wait a minute.
你那颗是安眠药
Is that the sleeping pill,
还是我的紧急自杀太空药
or is that my emergency space pill that kills you?
两种都能让我闭眼安眠
Either way, I'll get some shut-eye.
麦克斯  不许
Max, no!
不许你抛下我一人在这世界上
You are not gonna die and leave me here alone.
在没有监护人带领的情况下  我还没搞懂
I still don't know how to go east on the "L" Train
怎么坐L火号车去东边
without a chaperone.
麦克斯  现在是凌晨3点30分
Max, it's 3:30 A.M.,
睡眠教练卡洛琳
and sleep coach Caroline here
最晚能让你在3点45分安然入睡哦
will have you asleep by 3:45 the latest.
你不是应该泡个热水澡吗
You're supposed to be taking a hot bath.
本来是  但当我把塞子塞进去时
I was, but when I put the stopper in,
有东西又把它给顶出来了
something pushed it back out again.
药片在哪里
Where's that pill?
我藏在身上呢
I've got it on my person,
如果这些都不管用  我就把它给你
and if this doesn't work I'll give it to you.
为了药片  整只手伸入你洞内找
Oh, I'll go elbow-deep for that pill.
我都会做哦
And don't think I won't.
麦克斯  这是你的新寝具
Max, meet your new sheets.
新寝具  这是...
New sheets, meet--
用不着互相介绍  我又不是神经病人
Don't make me meet the sheets. I'm not a mental patient.
如果我是  那住的地方会比这好多了
If I was, I'd be living in a much nicer place.
而且我所有的枕套都会有花边
And all my pillowcases would have edges.
哇  你的枕套居然有花边啊
Wow, even your pillowcase had an edge.
你的枕套到底是什么样的
What was it like anyway?
就像是你新睡衣下面那样
It was kinda like the end of your new PJs,
但你的睡衣是我见过最基的东西
but not the queerest thing I've ever seen.
还点蜡烛  你以为我们是女巫吗
A candle? What are we, witches?
现在想象自己处在一个轻松美丽的地方
Now, imagine yourself in a relaxed, beautiful place.
让呼吸自由进出
Breathe in and out.
吸气  呼气
In and out.
听着  手指篮姑娘唯一了解的事情
Look, if there's one thing old finger basket know how to do
那就是"进跟出"
it's in and out.
把药片给我
Gimme the pill.
我还没说完呢
I'm not finished yet.
但先提醒你
But just so you know,
那颗药片在一个小时里变色了叁次了
that pill has changed colors three times in the last hour.
要么会吃死人  要么就是五彩糖球
So it's either deadly, or an Everlasting Gobstopper.
我真是被你气死了  你就拿走我唯一一样
I am so mad at you. You took my one thing.
我生命中有特别意义的东西
That pillowcase was my one special thing.
我的人生中  人们从我身边拿走了很多东西
In my whole life of people taking things away from me,
唯有那个枕套从来没人会拿
that was the one thing no one took,
而现在我再也睡不着了
and now I'm never gonna sleep again.
我爱睡觉
And I love sleeping.
做梦是我离有线电视最接近的时刻了
Dreaming is the closest thing I have to cable TV.
够了  麦克斯
Enough, Max!
在你对"一张床单"[屎]过分依赖的事情上
I've been very patient with this weird attachment you have
我已经够耐心了
to this little piece of sheet.
你才是"一坨屎"呢
You're a piece of sheet.
在我失去一切时  我懂得两个道理
Listen, if I learned anything when I lost everything,
那就是  第一
It's that, "A," there's no wiggle room
白干酪的保质期限说到就到了
when it comes to cottage cheese expiration dates,
第二  你不能过于依赖物质事物
And "B," You can't get attached to material things.
得了吧  接发不算吗
Okay, extensions.
这话什么意思
What does that mean?
意思就是准确来说
It means that your material things
你依赖的事物粘了你满脑袋
are literally attached to your head.
完全不一样好吗
Not the same thing at all.
你满脑子都是你对那个枕套的依赖
Your dependency on that pillowcase is all in your head,
而你却不需要它
you don't need it.
那你也不需要这个
Oh. You don't need this.
你欠我14块
You owe me $14.
先记账吧
Run a tab.
我才不要坐在这里忍受你的侮辱
I'm not about to sit here and take this abuse
就因为你对一个枕套有着病态的依赖心理
because you have an unhealthy attachment to a pillowcase.
晚安  马里布芭比
Good night, Malibu Barbie.
希望你不是想要侮辱我
I hope you're not trying to insult me,
因为你这话是在赞美我
because she's gorgeous!
对了  郑重声明
And for the record,
我对我的头发才没有什么病态的依赖心理
I do not have an unhealthy attachment to my hair.
是吗
Oh, really.
你个禽兽
You're a monster!
对不起  人家睡不着嘛
I'm sorry, I can't sleep.
只要你把药片给我  我就没事了
I'll be fine. Just give me the pill.
只是你心理作用
No! It's all in your head!
快去睡觉
Go to sleep!
我用绳子把门把和我的床绑到一起
I tied the doorknob to my bed with a rope
然后把卧室所有的窗户都关上了
and locked all the bedroom windows.
你是想伤害我  还是想让我欲火焚身啊
Are you trying to hurt me or turn me on?
你要做好心理准备  厄尔
Brace yourself, Earl.
麦克斯今天上班的心情不会太好哦
When Max gets here, she will not be in a good mood.
卡洛琳  如果我想跟一群天天好心情的人共事
Caroline, if I wanted to work around people in a good mood,
我早去谷歌上班了
I'd go work at Google.
她从昨天开始就睡不着
She hasn't slept since yesterday
因为我不愿意给她安眠药  她现在超级火大
and is furious because I won't give her a sleeping pill.
明智之举
Smart move.
安眠药只会把人搞得更糟
Sleeping pills mess you up.
我曾经吃过一次  结果在一天后醒来
I took one once, woke up a day later
发现自己科尼岛的云霄飞车上
on the roller coaster ride in Coney Island.
我喜欢云霄飞车
I love roller coasters.
但得是坐在座位里我才喜欢啊
Me too, when I'm in a seat.
你们好啊
Oh, hello!
你们俩今晚好吗
How are you two tonight?
天啊  她太友善了
Oh, no. She's nice.
她肯定从哪里搞到安眠药了
She must've gotten a pill somewhere.
不  我没吃药  只是想明白了
No. No pills. Just had some clarity.
-请跟我来  -好吧
- Follow me, please. - Oh, okay.
你是"抽"明白了  还是"吸"明白了
Did you smoke or snort this clarity?
既然你这么好  送我新床单
Yeah, since you were nice enough to get me new sheets,
我也有东西作为回礼  给
I got you something in return. Here.
这是表示歉意的同时
Oh, is this like an apology,
兼表示谢意吗
thank you kind of thing?
给我看好了
Now watch.
人接受礼物时就应该这么优雅
This is how one graciously accepts a gift.
这是啥玩意啊
What the hell is this?
假发
A wig?
不然就是你剥了80年代拉拉的头皮
Either that or you scalped a lesbian from the '80s.
是的  我一把抓住她的波洛领带
Yep, I grabbed her bolo tie
然后爬上她的垫肩[当年流行]
and climbed up on her shoulder pads.
你夺走让我有安全感的东西
You took away my security thing--
我的枕套
the pillowcase--
所以现在我要夺走让你有安全感的东西
So now I'm taking away your security thing--
你的头发
your hair.
你今晚可以戴着那玩意
You can wear that on your head tonight
然后告诉我一切都只是心理作用可以克服
and then tell me again how this is all in my head.
你非得买人家店里最丑的那一顶吗
Did you have to get the ugliest one they had?
3毛7的东西  你还想要求什么
What do you want for 37 cents?
好吧  我会把这个烂玩意顶头上
Fine! I'll put this roadkill on my head
向你证明  我的价值不只是这头秀发
Just to prove to you that I am so much more than my hair.
还有我的态度  心灵  大脑和勇气
I am my attitude, my spirit, my brain, my bravery.
-戴上它  -麦克斯  我好害怕
- Put it on. - Max, I'm scared.
快  把刘海拨到后面[从后面搞]
Go. The bangs go in the back.
我就喜欢这种女人
That's my kinda woman.
科布沙拉  上菜
Cobb salad, pick-up!
苏菲
Uh...hey, Sophie.
你是知道有黑手党寡妇折扣  才穿着这样吗
Are you here for the mafia widow discount?
厄尔  我在保持低调
Earl, I'm incognito.
偷偷来给麦克斯送药的
I'm making a drug drop for Max.
麦克斯  你的药[毒品]来了
Hey, Max! I got your drugs!
谢啦
Thanks.
我爱死你永远能找到一套
And I love that you have an outfit
适合我让你干的事的衣服
for everything I ask you to do.
那个金发缉毒特警呢  麦克斯
Where's the blonde narc, Max?
天啊
Oh, my God!
卡洛琳加入保龄球队了吗
Did Caroline join a bowling team?
麦克斯  不行
Max! No!
糟糕
Aw, crap!
被罗德・斯图尔特逮个正着
Rod Stewart just busted us.
英国老派摇滚歌手  发型类似
让她爽一下吧  有啥大不了的  老古板
Let her have some fun. What's the big deal, square?
因为她觉得自己需要这药的理由
The big deal is that Max thinks she needs these pills
是因为我丢了她的小被被
because I threw away her blankie.
那是个枕套  有它我才能睡着
It was a pillowcase, and I need it to sleep.
她得摸着才能睡
She has to rub it.
在波兰
In Poland,
我也有样小东西
I had this little thing that I liked to tickle
喜欢在睡觉前玩
before I went to sleep.
但也被我姨母扔了
But my aunt threw it away.
那是什么
What was it?
我的诺拉表妹
It was my cousin Nora.
-把药给我  -不要
- Give me the pills. - Nope.
麦克斯  你是错的  瞧我
And, Max, you were wrong. See?
我一点都不依赖我的头发
I'm not attached to my hair.
老实说  我开始爱上我的新发型
In fact, I am loving my new look.
我是个懒得打扮的单亲母亲
Am I a single mom trying to keep it simple?
或是助理地方检察官呢
Am I an assistant D.A. in over my head?
又或是邦・乔飞故事里的查理兹・塞隆
Or am I Charlize Theron in the Jon Bon Jovi story?
或许吧  我完全不介意
Maybe, and I'm fine with it.
因为我一点也不看重我的头发
'cause I am not my hair.
天啊  火鸡叁明治帅哥  掩护我
Oh, my god, turkey club cutie! Hide me!
戴着难看的假发  双膝跪地
On your knees in a bad wig.
姑娘  我也有过这样的经历
Listen, girl, I've been there.
不  我只是不想被人看见
No, I just don't wanna be seen.
卡洛琳  卡洛琳  我爱你
Caroline, Caroline, I love you,
但我听不下去了
But I can't hear anymore.
这顶假发即使在70年代  也让人不忍直视
That hair was hard enough to look at in the '70s.
好吧  你是对的  我是错的
Fine! You were right, I was wrong.
帮我把假发脱下来  我不能让他见我这样
Now help me get this off. He can't see me like this.
没错  把药给我
That's right, gimme the pills.
麦克斯  不  你不需要
Max, no. You don't need them.
我们都不知道这药哪来的
We don't know where they've been.
好吧
Fine!
那我回家睡觉
I'm going home to try to sleep.
既然这都是你的错  那你来替我上班吧
Since this is all your fault, you can finish my shift.
你自己上班吧
You're on your own,
80年代肥皂剧那个住在对面街的女人
lady who lived across the street from Al Bundy
不得不说  我真佩服我自己也能接发
I gotta say, I'm pretty impressed I can do this.
其实没那么难嘛
It's not so hard.
我不懂钱妮丝干嘛老抱怨
I don't know what Chanice is always bitching about.
或许她就是个爱抱怨的贱人吧
I guess that's who she is.
真不敢相信我到现在还没睡着
I can't believe I still haven't slept.
我这辈子都别想睡觉了
I'm gonna be awake forever.
最后会像那部电影《唤醒》  但我是想睡死过去
It's gonna be like that movie Awakenings, but not at all.
电影讲述的是一名医生在偶然的机会通过一种尚未通过临床研究的药物
使得病人走出了几十年的梦境
麦克斯  你可以摸我
Max, you can rub me.
哇  那顶拉拉假发把你掰弯啦
Wow, that wig changed you.
不  是这里
No, here.
摸我睡衣下面的花边
Rub the edge on the bottom of my jammie top
-把它当成是你的枕套  -不要
- like it's your pillowcase. - No.
如果我摸你睡衣的下面
If I rub the bottom of your jammies,
那我就会变成无下限
that would be my bottom.
火鸡叁明治帅哥没有约我出去
Turkey club cutie didn't ask me out,
可能是因为我的头发被假发弄得太乱了
probably because my hair was so messed up from the wig.
别对自己那么苛刻
Don't be so hard on yourself.
也有可能是讨厌你性格啊
it could've been your personality too.
你真的觉得他是因为头发才喜欢你吗
You really think he only liked you for your hair?
反正我是
I only like me for my hair.
早说了吧  你就是爱它
Told you. You're attached to it.
我超级爱我的头发
So attached to it!
用手转着玩  甩着玩  翻着玩
Twirling it, tossing it, flipping it.
在我的脖子  肩膀还有后背感觉它
Feeling it on my neck, on my shoulders, on my back.
没有光滑发髻的卡洛琳・钱宁
Caroline Channing without the option
就不是卡洛琳・钱宁了
of a sleek updo is not Caroline Channing.
对不起啦
And I'm sorry.
很抱歉我因为
I'm sorry I judged you
你对某物过于依赖而批评你
for having an attachment to something
而我也没好到哪去
when I'm no better.
抱歉我把你亲爱的寝具扔了
And I'm sorry I got rid of your sweet sheets.
麦克斯
Max.
Max?
晚安  麦克斯
Night, Max.
为什么啊
Whyyyy?
为什么我就不能拥有点好东西呢
Why can't I ever have anything nice?